Two Worlds. One Dream.
StreetDance 3D is a music, romance, drama film directed by Max Giwa.
In order to win the Street Dance Championships, a dance crew is forced to work with
ballet dancers from the Royal Dance School in exchange for rehearsal space.
Carly, played by Nichola Burley.
Tomas, played by Richard Winsor.
Jay, played by Ukweli Roach.
Fred, played by Frank Harper.
Eddie, played by George Sampson.
Helena, played by Charlotte Rampling.
StreetDance 3D (also called StreetDance) is a 2010 British 3D comedy drama film
directed by Max Giwa and Dania Pasquini, and written by Jane English.
It was released on 21 May 2010 in RealD 3D, XpanD 3D and Dolby 3D.
Britain's Got Talent stars George Sampson, Diversity and Flawless
made their debut appearances to the big screen.
A production of Vertigo Films in association with BBC Films, the soundtrack features
alternative acts N-Dubz, Tinie Tempah, Lightbulb Thieves and Chipmunk.
A sequel, StreetDance 2, was released on 30 March 2012.
The film explores themes of ballet dancer, street
dance, woman director, dance group.
The tone is emotional.